总统猥亵了你? 不是
POTUS groped you? - No.
总统没那个种来猥亵我
POTUS wouldn't have the balls to grope me.
他知道他说了谎?
He knew and he lied?
等等 等等 知道什么?对什么说谎?
Wait, wait, knew what? Lied about what?
总统知道那个学生是间谍
POTUS knew that the student was a spy
并且没有通知国会的情报委员会
and didn't inform the Congressional Intel Committee.
去他的!去他的! 你们刚才说什么?
- Shit! Shit! - What were you talking about?
Osmo猥亵了我
Osmo groped me.
去他的!
Shit!
我们要
We need to rain down the full might
把核武库的全部火力倾向芬兰
of our nuclear arsenal on Finland.
Mm-hmm.
这就是另一件我忘记告诉你的事情
That's the other thing I forgot to tell you.
我们要炸平芬兰
We're gonna blow up Finland.
我能为您做什么? 他妈的你去哪了?
Can I help you? Where the fuck you been?
别跟我说 你一直在做民调
Don't tell me. You've been polling.